{
  "theme": [
    {
      "Questions": {
        "theme": [
          {
            "Question": "What color were the pills Pac-Man eats?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Multicolored",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Blue",
              "Yellow",
              "Red"
            ],
            "Explanation": "The pills Pac-Man eats are depicted as multicolored in the game, indicating his feasting on various fruits and food items."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Who played the lead role in 'The Matrix' trilogy?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Keanu Reeves",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Will Smith",
              "Brad Pitt",
              "Tom Cruise"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Keanu Reeves portrayed the iconic character Neo in 'The Matrix' trilogy, gaining significant praise for his performance."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which artist is known as the 'Queen of Pop'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Madonna",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Beyoncé",
              "Rihanna",
              "Taylor Swift"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Madonna, with her prolific career and immense impact on music and culture, earned the title 'Queen of Pop' globally."
          },
          {
            "Question": "What is the name of Harry Potter's best friend?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Ron Weasley",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Draco Malfoy",
              "Hermione Granger",
              "Neville Longbottom"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Ron Weasley, portrayed by Rupert Grint, is Harry Potter's loyal and adventure-seeking best friend throughout the series."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which TV show featured a character named Walter White?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Breaking Bad",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "The Sopranos",
              "Stranger Things",
              "Grey's Anatomy"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Bryan Cranston played the iconic character Walter White, a high school chemistry teacher turned methamphetamine manufacturer, in 'Breaking Bad'."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Who is the youngest Kardashian-Jenner sister?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Kylie Jenner",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Kendall Jenner",
              "Khloé Kardashian",
              "Kim Kardashian"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Kylie Jenner is the youngest of the Kardashian-Jenner siblings and has become a prominent figure in fashion and beauty industries."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which artist released the album 'Lemonade'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Beyoncé",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Rihanna",
              "Adele",
              "Taylor Swift"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Beyoncé's 'Lemonade' received critical acclaim for its exploration of personal and social themes, and it became a cultural phenomenon."
          },
          {
            "Question": "What is the signature sound of Michael Jackson's 'Beat It'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Eddie Van Halen's Guitar Solo",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Synthesizer Riffs",
              "Funky Bassline",
              "Whistle Melody"
            ],
            "Explanation": "The electrifying guitar solo played by Eddie Van Halen is the iconic signature sound of Michael Jackson's 'Beat It'."
          },
          {
            "Question": "In which movie did Heath Ledger play the Joker?",
            "TrueAnswer": "The Dark Knight",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Batman Begins",
              "The Dark Knight Rises",
              "Suicide Squad"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Heath Ledger's portrayal of the Joker in 'The Dark Knight' is considered one of the greatest performances in film history and earned him a posthumous Academy Award."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Who directed the 'Star Wars' prequel trilogy?",
            "TrueAnswer": "George Lucas",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "J.J. Abrams",
              "Steven Spielberg",
              "Christopher Nolan"
            ],
            "Explanation": "George Lucas directed the 'Star Wars' prequel trilogy, delving into the origins of iconic characters and the rise of Darth Vader."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which fictional city is home to Batman's crime-fighting adventures?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Gotham City",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Metropolis",
              "Central City",
              "Star City"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Gotham City, a dark and corrupt metropolis, serves as the primary setting for Batman's vigilante activities and is populated by iconic villains and heroes."
          },
          {
            "Question": "What band performed the song 'Bohemian Rhapsody'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Queen",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "The Beatles",
              "Led Zeppelin",
              "Pink Floyd"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Queen, led by frontman Freddie Mercury, produced the operatic rock masterpiece 'Bohemian Rhapsody', which remains a timeless classic."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which actress portrayed the character Katniss Everdeen in 'The Hunger Games'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Jennifer Lawrence",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Emma Watson",
              "Shailene Woodley",
              "Daisy Ridley"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Jennifer Lawrence's portrayal of Katniss Everdeen in 'The Hunger Games' trilogy contributed to the franchise's immense success and her rise as a leading Hollywood actress."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Who directed the film 'Inception'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Christopher Nolan",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Quentin Tarantino",
              "James Cameron",
              "Martin Scorsese"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Christopher Nolan wrote and directed the mind-bending thriller 'Inception', known for its intricate plot and visual effects."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which pop icon is known for the song 'Like a Prayer'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Madonna",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Whitney Houston",
              "Celine Dion",
              "Cher"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Madonna's 'Like a Prayer' sparked controversy and acclaim for its blending of religious imagery and pop music, adding to her status as a cultural provocateur."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Who voiced the character 'Shrek' in the animated film series?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Mike Myers",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Eddie Murphy",
              "Cameron Diaz",
              "Chris Farley"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Mike Myers provided the distinctive Scottish accent and comedic timing for the lovable ogre Shrek, contributing to the film's endearing appeal."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which film director created the 'Alien' and 'Blade Runner' franchises?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Ridley Scott",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "James Cameron",
              "Steven Spielberg",
              "George Lucas"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Ridley Scott's visionary direction gave birth to the iconic 'Alien' and 'Blade Runner' franchises, shaping the sci-fi genre for decades to come."
          },
          {
            "Question": "What is the highest-grossing film directed by a woman?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Wonder Woman",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Frozen",
              "Captain Marvel",
              "Mulan"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Directed by Patty Jenkins, 'Wonder Woman' became the highest-grossing film helmed by a woman at the time of its release, marking a significant milestone for female directors in the superhero genre."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which celebrity is known for the reality TV show 'Keeping Up with the Kardashians'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Kim Kardashian",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Paris Hilton",
              "Nicole Richie",
              "Kylie Jenner"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Kim Kardashian, alongside her family, gained widespread fame and notoriety through the reality TV show 'Keeping Up with the Kardashians', significantly impacting celebrity culture and social media influence."
          },
          {
            "Question": "What animated series features the character Bart Simpson?",
            "TrueAnswer": "The Simpsons",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Family Guy",
              "South Park",
              "Bob's Burgers"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Bart Simpson, known for his mischievous antics and catchphrases, is a central character in the long-running animated series 'The Simpsons'."
          }
        ]
      }
    }
  ]
}